eoearth.org 2013-05-26

# Privacy Policy

This article has been reviewed by the following Topic Editor: Cutler J. Cleveland

The [Environmental Information Coalition (EIC)](http://www.eoearth.org/article/Environmental_Information_Coalition "http://www.eoearth.org/article/Environmental_Information_Coalition") recognizes that privacy is important. This policy covers how the EIC treats personal information that we may collect from your use of the Encyclopedia of Earth, the Earth Portal, or any other web site in the Digital Universe. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

The EIC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated organizations except under the following circumstances: 

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the EIC's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at [eoe@eoearth.org](mailto:eoe@eoearth.org "mailto:eoe@eoearth.org"). 

## Citation

Cutler J. Cleveland (Lead Author);Cutler J. Cleveland (Topic Editor) "Privacy Policy". In: Encyclopedia of Earth. Eds. Cutler J. Cleveland (Washington, D.C.: Environmental Information Coalition, National Council for Science and the Environment). First published in the Encyclopedia of Earth November 13, 2008; Last revised Date November 13, 2008; Retrieved May 26, 2013 <<http://www.eoearth.org/article/Privacy_Policy>>

## The Author

[ Cutler J. Cleveland  is Professor of Earth and Environment at Boston University, where he also is on the faculty of the Center for Energy and Environmental Studies. Professor Cleveland is Editor-in-Chief of the Encyclopedia of Energy (Elsevier, 2004), winner of an American Library Association award, the Dictionary of Energy (Elsevier, 2005), Handbook of Energy (Elsevier, forthcoming), and is the Founding Editor-in-Chief of the Encyclopedia of Earth.  He is the recipient of the Adelma ... (Full Bio)
